打得不错  兄弟
Good work, bro.
- 酷  哥们  - 这次感觉不错  兄弟
- Cool, man. - Good sesh, man.
别担心  我下周再找你
No worries. I'll catch up with you next week.
嘿  雷
Hey, ray!
怎么了  哥们
Yeah, mate?
你能帮我看下孩子们吗
Yeah, um...You wanna help me out with the kids?
- 好啊  - 谢谢了  哥们
- Yeah, alright. Yeah. - Appreciate it, man.
- 哪个小孩  - 就那一帮孩子
- Which one? - Just take that group.
- 我来看这些  - 好
- I'll grab these guys. - Alright.
就这么办
Let's do it.
好了  我们要做的是
Alright, so what we'll do is
我们会练习一会轻型拳击
we're just gonna do some light sparring.
所以别想着打倒对方  懂了吗
So don't try to knock each other out, right?
你们几个一起  好吗
So you guys go together, right?
记住友谊第一
And just keep it nice and friendly.
我们要做一点这个  做一点那个
And we'll...Do a bit of this, do a bit of that.
好了  让我们看看你的身手吧
Alright, let's see what you've got.
好的  好的
Ok. Ok.
好的  我会出几个拳
Alright. Alright, I'm gonna throw a few.
- 准备好了吗  - 准备好了
- You ready? - Yep.
好的不错  坚持住
Ooh, ok. Yep, right. Yeah, hang on.
- 非常好  非常好  - 谢谢
- Pretty good, pretty good! - Thanks.
所以  你练拳击多久了
So, how long you been doing this for?
- 一个月左右  - 没学过别的
- About a month. - Is that all?
我几年前
I used to do jujitsu
学过柔道
for a couple of years before this, though.
好的  想试试你能不能摔倒对手吗
Oh, ok. You wanna see if you can get a takedown?
- 当然  - 好的  来吧
- Sure! - Cool. Alright. Yep.
你还好吗  老伙计
You ok, old man?
还好
Yep.
你应该拍地认输的
Should have tapped.
就是没有啊
No shit.
好了  散开吧  继续训练  各位
come on, let's go. Back to work, guys.
回器材的回器材  回拳击台的回拳击台  赶紧的
Back to the gym, back to the ring. Let's do it.
先生
中间人
第二季
第一集
翻译： Krystal
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
翻译： 岛岛
翻译： 文睿菌
把手放我膝盖上
Feel my knee.
校对： 岛岛
特效： 转轮手枪
- 怎么了  - 放上去
- Why? - Just feel it.
时间轴： 麦斯
你觉得我膝盖肥了吗  脂肪多吗
Do they feel fat? Do you think they feel fat?
- 不怎么肥  - 不怎么肥吗
- Not really. - Not really?
你怎么不直接说不肥
Why didn't you say no?
因为不怎么肥听起来
'cause when you say 'not really',
就像是很肥
it kinda sounds like they are fat.
别不耐烦
Don't get shitty.
- 别不耐烦  - 我没有不耐烦
-  don't get shitty! - I'm not shitty.
你还好吗
are you right?
很好
yep.
你能不要冲着我的脸放屁吗
Do you mind not farting in my face?
我可没有冲着你的脸放屁
I didn't fart in your face.
别这样
Come on, don't.
很恶心
It's disgusting.
你应该为此感到开心
You should be happy I fart in front of you.
我为什么要开心
Why should I be happy?
我只有在亲近的人面前才会放屁
Well, I only fart in front of people I'm comfortable with.
就算你觉得这是亲近
Just 'cause you feel comfortable doing something
也不代表你应该这么做
doesn't mean that you should do it.
所以如果我
So if I...
如果我觉得
If I felt comfortable...
在你胸前拉屎很放松  我就应该这么做吗
..Taking a shit on your chest, does it mean I should do it?
你想在我胸前拉屎吗
Do you wanna take a shit on my chest?
也许吧
Maybe.
是吗
Yeah?
这样子的话
Well?
我不介意
Go for it.
别挑衅我  哥们
Don't dare me, pal.
我就是在挑衅你
I'm daring ya.
好啊
Alright.
- 准备好了吗  - 准备好了
- Ready? - Yeah, ready.
但你得先把裤子脱了
But you gotta take your pants off first
因为你不能拉裤裆里
'cause you're just gonna end up shitting in your pants.
怎么了
hey?
你这个傻子
You're an idiot!
- 你去哪  - 尿尿
- where you going? - I gotta have a wee.
- 你半小时前尿过了  - 谢谢您还算时间
- You weed half an hour ago. - Thanks for keeping score!
我好几个小时没尿了
I haven't peed for hours.
挺好的  没人要比这个
Good for you. It's not a competition.
不  要比
Yeah, it is.
好了  亲我一下
Alright. Give us a kiss.
我今天不想上学
I don't wanna go to school today.
为什么
Why not?
- 有什么事吗  - 没事
- What's going on? - Nothing.
如果出了什么事  你可以告诉我
If there's something going wrong, you can tell me.
说吧  怎么了
Come on. What's wrong?
学校里有个女孩对我很刻薄
There's a girl at school and she's mean to me all the time.
她干什么了
What's she doing?
她给我起了些外号之类的
She calls me names and stuff.
你跟你老师说过了吗
Have you told your teacher about it?
没有
No.
你想让我跟你老师说说吗
Do you want me to talk to her about it?
不用  我会告诉她的
No, I'll tell her.
好吧
Ok.
好吧  如果你有什么问题  亲爱的
Well, yeah, if you have any problems, darling,
你就去跟你老师说
you just talk to your teacher,
因为这就是老师的职责
'cause that's what she's there for.
- 好吗  - 好
- Ok? - Ok.
- 爱你  - 拜拜  爱你
- Mwah. Love ya. - 'bye. Love you.
上学愉快
Have a good day.
我的女朋友想和她的朋友们出去玩
So my girlfriend wanted to go out with her friends
比如女孩之夜  去夜店之类的
like, have a girls night out, go clubbing.
但是  我不喜欢她不带我自己出去玩
And, um...I don't really like her going out without me.
所以  我们开始为此吵架
So, yeah, we just started fighting about it.
所以为什么你不喜欢她自己出去玩
And why don't you like her going out without you?
这个嘛
Oh, well...
我就是不喜欢
..I just don't.
你不信任她
Do you not trust her?
我是说  她有没有出过轨
I mean, has she ever... Has she ever cheated on you?
没有
No.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
不  不是这个原因  我是说  至少我不知道她出轨
No, no, it's nothing like that. I mean...Not that I know of.
我想问题是
I guess the thing is, like...
好吧
Well...Yeah.
好吧  事实上  我确实不信任她
Yeah, actually, I guess I don't trust her.
你为什么不信任她
And why do you think that is?
呃
Well...
她很  就是  贼性感
..She's, like, really fuckin' sexy.
你知道  她出门的时候
You know, like, when she goes out,
她会穿那种很紧身很短的衣服
she wears these tiny little fuckin' outfits
你知道  让人浮想联翩
and, you know, they don't leave a whole lot to the imagination.
这样  看  我给你们看
Here, look. I'll show you.
- 这是她  - 老天
- This is her. - Oh, jesus christ!
- 她是个大美女啊  哥们  - 是啊
- She's a fuckin' stunner, mate. - Yeah.
我们看看
let's have a look.
天呐  哥们
Oh, holy shit, mate!
我老婆要长这样  我不可能让她出门
My missus looked like that, I'd never let her leave the house.
好了  谢谢  卡罗
Ok. Thank you, carlo.
所以  我和她一起出门的时候
so, like, when me and her go out together,
我就站在那呢  就会有男的
guys will come up and just start hitting on her
过来撩她
while I'm standing there.
上一个被我揍的男的就是因为这么撩她
You know, like, the last guy I bashed was because of that.
这个屌丝就这么突然过来
Like, this fuckin' bloke just comes up
然后就开始撩妹  就在我眼皮底下
and starts hitting on her right in front of me, you know?
- 我女朋友还很喜欢出这种风头  - 好的  所以
- And she loves the attention. - Right, so...
- 我能问你个问题吗  - 可以
- Can I ask you something? - Yeah.
她跟几个男的睡过
How many blokes has she slept with?
- 雷  - 没关系
- Ray. - That's alright.
差不多三四十个吧
Like, 30, 40.
怪不得你不信任她  哥们
No wonder you don't trust her, mate.
我是说  如果她睡过这么多男人
I mean, shit, if she's slept with that many blokes,
再多睡两个又有什么区别呢
what's to stop her from sleeping with a few more?
- 说到点子上了  - 雷  行了
- Exactly. - Ray, that's enough.
你想想  她出去玩  喝醉了
I mean, you know, she goes out, she gets drunk,
在你知道之前  她可以变成另外一个人
before you know it, she's fucking somebody else.
雷  你能不能别把你的厌女症传给别人
Ray...How about you keep your misogyny to yourself?
- 我的什么  - 厌女症
- My what? - Your misogyny.
那是什么东西
What's that?
根据词典
According to the dictionary,
厌女症指对女人的鄙视
a misogynist is a person who despises women.
我不鄙视女人
I don't despise women.
从我听到的来说
Well, from what I'm hearing here,
在你眼里女人不怎么样
it sounds like you don't think very highly of them.
我有女朋友  我还有女儿
I got a girlfriend, I got a daughter.
你在说什么  我恨他们吗  还是
What are you saying, like, I hate 'em or something? Or...
历史上有许多严重厌女的人
Plenty of history's great misogynists
都有女朋友或者女儿啊  雷
have had daughters and girlfriends, ray.
比如呢
Like who?
就很多人啊
Like plenty.
你说一个
Name one.
我觉得我们还是
I think we should, um...
继续吧
..Move on, uh...
雨果
Hugo?
我今天开车上班没出事故呢
I managed to drive to work today without incident.
太棒了
That's terrific.
布里特
Brit!
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
要不要来喝点茶吃点饭啊
Are you gonna come and have some tea or what?
你在干嘛啊
What are you doing?
怎么了
What's the matter?
这是谁放上的
Who put that up there?
- 谁干的  - 泰勒
-Who did that? -Taylor.
我真丑
爸爸  为什么她那么讨厌我
dad, why does she hate me so much?
不是所有人都会喜欢你的  知道吗
Look, not everybody's gonna like you, darling, ok?
你也不能强迫他们喜欢你
And you can't make people like you, ok?
但你可以让他们害怕你
But you can make them fear you.
我不想让别人害怕我
I don't want people to be scared of me.
我也不是说
Well, I'm not saying that, you know,
你要让所有人都害怕你
you should make everybody scared of you.
但如果大家不尊重你
But, um, if people don't respect you,
你就让他们害怕你
that's when you make 'em fear you.
所以如果大家尊重我了  我就不用让他们害怕了吗
So if people respect me, I don't need to scare them?
是的  但是如果大家
Yeah. Yeah, that's right. But if people...
你看啊  如果大家不尊重你
See, if people don't respect you,
但你还尊重的对待他们
and you still treat them with respect...
那你就是个门垫一样的
..Then you're a doormat.
- 懂吗  - 不懂什么意思
-If you understand what I mean.  -What does that mean?
门垫啊  就是受气包
Well, you know, like a doormat.
就是任人欺负  任人践踏的那种人
A doormat is a person who lets other people walk all over 'em.
你不会想成为这种人的
Ok? And that's not the kind of person you wanna be.
- 好吗  - 嗯
-Ok? -Mm-hm.
这次我替你解决了
I'm gonna take care of this problem for you, ok?
- 好  - 这个泰勒
-Ok. -This taylor...
皮皮节
年度医学美肤大促 9.9-9.29
新氧
医美
■
新人199元免单
○
-
看着我  宝贝
Look at me, darling.
不会再去烦你了 好吗
She's not gonna bother you again, ok?
- 好吗  我保证  - 好
-Alright? I promise you, ok? -Ok.
现在要不要来吃点东西了
Now, you wanna come and have some tea?
- 吃什么  - 披萨
-What are we having? -Pizza.
- 你做的吗  - 对啊
-Your ones? -Mm-hm.
- 带培根的吗  - 当然
-With bacon? -Course!
- 好吗  - 好的
-Ok! -Alright?
借过一下
'scuse me, guys.
谢谢  谢谢  抱歉
Thank you. Thank you. Sorry.
抱歉  借过
Sorry. Sorry, guys.
- 刚刚又进球了吗  - 是啊
-Was that another goal? -Yeah.
怎么都他么用手传球啊  我的天
What's up with all the fuckin' hand-passing, man?
好像在玩一个烫手的山芋
It's like a game of hot potato.
这些人倒是好好打啊
These blokes need to harden up!
每次一拿到球  就跟傻了一样
Every time they get the ball, they shit themselves.
塔蒂阿娜信息
网又很慢了  烦死了
我靠了
oh, shit.
哥们  帮我个忙
Mate, I need a favour.
干什么
What?
我需要你去我家
I need you to come around my place
给我电脑搞个密码
and put a password on me computer.
为啥
Why?
因为我看太多黄片了
'cause I'm watching too much fuckin' porn, man.
我每天都打飞机
Every day, I'm jerking off.
有时候一天两次
Twice a day sometimes.
我认真的
I'm fuckin' serious.
你为啥不自己选一个密码
Why don't you pick the password?
我要是知道密码  我不就又打开看了吗
'cause if I know the password, I'll just unblock it.
但如果你问我密码  我不会告诉你的
But if you ask me, I'm not gonna tell you.
对啊  这就是重点啊
I know. That's the whole point of it.
你看  又进了个球
That's it! Just score another goal!
赶紧的
Get onto it!
但你会烦气的
Well, don't get shitty.
- 不会的  - 你会烦气的
-I won't. -You will. You'll get shitty.
如果我不告诉你密码  你就烦烦气气的
If I don't tell you what the password is, you'll get shitty.
- 我不会的  - 你会的
-No, I won't. -Yes, you will.
好吧  我可能会的  但是无论如何
Yeah, alright, maybe I will, but no matter what,
都别告诉我就行了  好吧
just don't tell me, alright?
你要帮我拯救一下我的婚姻啊
And save my marriage, for god's sake.
喂  怎么了
what's up?
有地址吗
have you got an address?
谁啊
Who's that?
弗雷迪让我来的
Freddy sent me over.
- 弗雷迪让你来的 -  是啊
-Freddy sent you? -Yeah.
- 谁啊  - 我他么哪知道
-Man 2: Who is it, man? -Man: I don't fuckin' know!
干什么啊
Why?
你到底要不要让我进去
You wanna let me in, mate, or what?
- 他要干嘛  - 不知道啊
-What's he want? -I don't know!
你带路吧
after you.
你好吗
Man: H-how you doing?
挺好的  你好吗
Yeah, good, mate. How you doing?
- 好  - 这边
-Good. -That's the way.
嗯
Yeah.
弗雷迪一直给你们打电话来着
So freddy's been trying to call you.
对啊  我们好像电话没费了
Oh, yeah...I think we've run out of credit, eh?
抱歉啊
Sorry, man.
好吧
alright.
抱歉
Sorry.
你们是不是应该替他干一个活儿的
So you were supposed to do a job for him or something?
是啊  活儿干完了
Oh. Yeah, yeah, job's done.
- 是啊  - 你要看看吗
-Oh, yeah! -Do you wanna see?
- 好吗 - 来这边
-Yeah? -Yeah, come this way, man.
我们本来要把他扔到山上的
so, uh, we were gonna dump him in the hills
- 但是太亮了 - 太阳出来了
but it got light - like, the sun came up.
就把他带回这里了
So we brought him back here.
等到天一黑  我们就去处理掉他
But as soon as it gets dark, we're gonna go get rid of him.
车哪来的
How hot's the car?
什么意思
What do you mean?
- 车是什么时候偷得  - 这是我的车
-Well, when did you steal it? -Oh, it's my car.
是我们的车啊  我们的
It's our car. It's our car.
喂
yello?
你是不是脑子进水了
What do you think you're doing?
什么
What?
你现在让这些傻蛋去杀人了啊
You're using these idiots to do hits now?
没有啊  我就是给他们的机会
No, mate, I just thought I would
看看他们干的怎么样
give them a go and see how they went.
好  那我来告诉你他们干的怎么样
Oh, ok. Well, I'll tell you how they went, mate.
他们把这人弄来了  杀了
They've grabbed this guy, they've killed him,
也不知道这人是谁
whoever he was,
现在呢  尸体就放在车库里的
and now they've got him in the boot of their car
车后备箱  因为他们感觉
in their garage because they didn't feel like
还不想把尸体处理掉呢
getting rid of the body just yet.
好吧  你先别激动呢  哥们
Yeah, alright. Set...Settle down, will ya, mate?
别他么让我别激动
Don't fuckin' tell me to settle down.
把我电话挂了
-Hung up on me!
喂
yello?
那个啥
Funny.
抱歉啊  哥们
Look, I'm sorry, mate, ok?
我没以为你会介意我这次用他们的
I didn't think you'd mind me using them on this one.
他们只收你价钱的四分之一
I mean, they charge a quarter what you do, alright?
我这周手头有点紧啊
And, I mean, I'm having a bad week this week.
大哥  你过去这二十年哪天手头不紧
Mate, you've been having a bad week for the last 20 years.
是啊是啊
Yeah, I know. I know.
- 那你弥补一下啊  - 怎么搞
-Well, do something about it! -Like what?
我不知道  关我屁事
I don't know. Not my problem.
那你想怎么办啊
So, what do you wanna do?
我不知道啊  你说啊  我又看不到什么情况
I don't know, you tell me. I can't read it from here.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
这俩都吸毒吸嗨了  大哥
Well, they're drug-fucked, mate.
如果他们被抓了  会把你也供出来的
If they get pinched, they're gonna roll on you.
那好吧  挖个坑
Yeah, ok - well, dig a hole,
把死人买了  把他俩也一起给埋了
put the dead guy in and...And put the other two in with him.
好的
Alright.
这得花我多少钱
How much is this gonna cost me?
九万
90.
- 九万   - 对啊  一人三万
-90?! -Yeah. 30 each, mate.
别人我都要四万一个人的
I'd charge anybody else 40 each.
那很感谢你啊
Yeah, ok, and I appreciate that,
但是你又不用干那么多活啊
but, look, it's not like you've gotta do a lot of work here.
其实一个人已经死了的啊
You know? I mean, one of them's dead already.
对啊  但我还得埋了他啊
Yeah, but I've still gotta bury him.
我知道  但你说的是杀人再埋起来的价钱啊
Sure, but you're charging me like you've gotta kill him!
好吧
Alright.
1万块处理掉那个死人
10 to get rid of the dead guy.
剩下俩人每人3万块  一共7万
30 each for the other two. 70.
谢谢你给我走了折扣价  伙计
Ok, and I appreciate the discount there, mate.
但是另外那两个人
But the other two guys
我是说  你又不需要
I mean, you know, it's not like you've gotta
挖三个洞  是不是
dig three holes, you know?
你只需要挖一个洞  然后把他们全埋进去就行
You're only gonna put 'em all in the one hole.
但我得挖一个大点儿的洞
But I've gotta dig a much bigger hole.
让他们去挖不就好了
Well, get them to dig it.
你怎么不过来  自己挖这个洞呢
Why don't you come down here and you can dig it?
我才不去  为什么要让我
I'm not gonna... Why would I...
虚伪的小滑头
Fuckin' slimy little prick.
又特么挂我电话了
Hung up on me again.
- 喂  - 6万
- hello? - 60.
6万5  不同意就拉倒
65. Take it or leave it.
行吧  成交
yeah, deal.
我可不想等到半年后才拿到这笔钱
And I don't wanna wait six months for my money either.
我明白  下周就把钱给你
Yeah, I know. You'll have the money next week.
你知道你让我不爽的一点是什么吗
You know the thing that shits me about you?
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
只有一点吗
There's only one thing?
你在我这儿跟我为一分钱讨价还价
You haggle over every cent you've gotta pay me, right,
结果却到赌场里
and then you go down to the casino
把10万块挥霍一空
and you blow 100 grand like it's nothing.
我明白  我明白
Yeah, I know, I know.
你明白个屁
Oh, you know.
好了  挂了
Alright. 'bye.
我得去找辆车
I'm going to get a car.
直接用我们的就行  伙计
Oh, just use ours, mate!
我不能用你们的车
I can't use yours.
为什么不行
why not?
为什么啊
Why not?
我也不知道  伙计
I don't know, man.
- 把他抬起来  - 我抬着呢
- lift him up! - I am, man.
好了吗
Got him?
你个蠢货
Oh, you fuckin' idiot!
闭嘴吧  要不你来抬着他的脑袋
Shut up, man! You wanna take the head?
天呐  太臭了
Oh, man, this stinks!
你和你前妻关系怎么样
How do you get on with your ex?
还可以  她再婚了  但是
Oh, not too bad. She's remarried, but...
我们关系还可以
yeah, we get on alright.
我有个  我有个女儿
I got a... I got a daughter.
- 是吗  - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
她多大了
How old is she?
她有  六岁了吧
She's, um... She's six, eh?
她叫艾瓦
Ava.
- 真漂亮  - 是啊
- Beautiful. - Yeah.
长得像她妈妈
She gets that from her mum there.
- 你能见得到她吗  - 不能
- You see her? - Nah.
- 说真的  现在见不到了  - 怎么回事
- Not anymore, really. - How come?
- 我前妻不让我见她  伙计  - 是吗
- Oh, the ex won't let me, man. - Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
这样挺好的  伙计  因为
That's cool, man. Like...
我知道我是个混蛋
I know I'm a fuck-up.
你得戒掉毒品  伙计
Just need to get off the drugs, mate.
谁说不是呢  该死的
Yeah, tell me about it, bro. Fuck!
我跟你说  伙计
Tell you, man,
过去的这24小时
this last 24 hours, eh,
我并不适合做这种事
I'm not cut out for this shit, eh.
我不是这样的人  没有冒犯你的意思
This is not me, like... No offence, eh.
这不是所有人都能干的  伙计
Hey, it's not for everybody, mate.
所以你是从小就在悉尼长大吗
So are you, like, from sydney originally?
不是  我家在乡下
Nah, country boy.
那怎么到这儿来了
What brought you up here?
主要是为了工作  但是
Oh, work mainly, but...
皮皮节
年度医学美肤大促 9.9-9.29
新氧
医美
■
新人199元免单
○
-
也不是不想将来再回到乡下
Yeah, wouldn't mind getting back to the country one day,
但我女儿和我弟弟在这里  所以
but I got my daughter here and my brother, so...
- 我也有个弟弟  伙计  - 是吗
- Oh, I got a bro as well, man! - Mmm?
他在珀斯住着
Yeah, he's, like, back in perth.
- 是么  - 他是个音乐天才  伙计
- Yeah. - He's a fuckin' muso, man.
他非常厉害
He's killing it, eh.
你有听过这个乐队吗
Have you heard of the band more or less?
没有
Nuh.
这是我们一起创办的  伙计  最开始只有我俩
Yeah, we started it together, man. Like, me and him.
我们曾一起写歌作曲啥的  还一起
Used to write songs together and shit. Fuckin' like...
举办演出  天呐
..Playing gigs, fuck, it's...
你喜欢玩儿乐器吗
Do you, like, play any musical instruments?
不咋喜欢
Nah.
我小时候试过学打鼓
Tried to learn how to play the drums when I was a kid.
我就是玩儿这个的
that's what I am, eh.
我是个鼓手
Yeah, I'm a drummer!
- 是吗  - 是的  伙计
- Yeah? - Yeah, man.
我可以教你哎
Yeah, I'll fuckin' teach you, hey!
好吧  但我没有成套的鼓乐器  所以
Yeah, well, I don't have a drum kit, so...
我也没有  伙计
Yeah, I don't either, man,
但如果你买一套的话  我可以教你
but if you buy one, then I'll teach you, hey.
- 我不收钱的  - 嗯嗯
- I wouldn't charge. - Mmm.
就好像  我们就像上架子鼓课一样
It'd just be... We'd have, like, fuckin' drum sessions.
身处这里是你的权利
* you have a right to be here *
不管你是否明白
* and whether or not *
它的奥秘
* it is clear to you... *
掐了
put it out.
去你妹的
Fuck off!
该死的
Shit!
- 不好意思哈  - 你他妈傻逼啊
- Sorry about that. - Fuckin' motherfucker!
骂得挺溜哈  伙计
Oh, good one, buddy.
怎么  你有意见吗
Yeah? What are you gonna do about it?
- 把枪收起来  - 你他妈闭嘴
- Put the fuckin' gun away. - Shut the fuck up!
- 瑞克  冷静点  伙计  - 不  你给我闭嘴
- Rick! Just chill out, man! - No, shut the fuck up!
我他妈才是老大  好吗
I'm the fuckin' boss here, ok?
- 好吧  好吧  - 你不是我的老大  好吗
- Ok, ok. - You're not the boss of me, ok?
什么鬼啊
What the fuck?
因为这世界充斥着欺诈
..For the world is full of trickery.
选自诗歌Desiderata（生命所渴求）
作者：Max Ehrmann
但是  不要因此而看不见人间美德
But let this not blind you to what virtue there is.
很多人为崇高理想而奋斗
Many persons strive for high ideals
生命到处都有英勇的事迹
and everywhere life is full of heroism.
做你自己
Be yourself.
尤其不要虚情假意
Especially do not feign affection.
但也不要把爱视为虚伪
Neither be cynical about love...
爱  却如青草般日久常在
..It is as perennial as the grass.
不轻视因年老而获得的阅历
Take kindly the counsel of the years,
并得体地舍弃年轻时拥有的东西
gracefully surrendering the things of youth.
培育心灵上的力量  以面对突然而来的不幸
Nurture strength of spirit to shield you in sudden misfortune.
但不要杞人忧天以致心神不宁
But do not distress yourself with imaginings.
众多的恐惧  源自疲乏和孤独
Many fears are born of fatigue and loneliness.
要既不踰矩  又善待自己
Beyond a wholesome discipline, be gentle with yourself.
你是宇宙的孩子
* you are a child... *
you are a child of the universe
身份不次于树木和星星
no less than the trees and the stars.
身处这里是你的权利
You have a right to be here.
不管你是否明白
* and whether or not... *
and whether or not it is clear to you...
它的奥秘
* it is clear to you... *
毫无疑问宇宙在按其规律展现自己
..No doubt the universe is unfolding as it should.
在按其规律
* unfolding *
展现自己
* as it should... *
因此  不管在你心中宇宙是什么模样
therefore be at peace with god,
和他和睦相处吧
whatever you conceive him to be.
也不管你怎样劳累和胸怀大志
And whatever your labours and aspirations,
在生命的烦嚣和困惑中
in the noisy confusion of life,
要保持心灵上的安宁
keep peace with your soul.
不管经历了多少伪善  苦役和破碎的梦
With all its sham, drudgery and broken dreams,
世界依然是美丽的
it is still a beautiful world.
要保持轻松开朗
Be careful.
要努力让自己快乐
Strive to be happy.
你是
* you are a child *
宇宙的孩子
* of the universe *
身份不次于树木和星星
* no less than the trees and the stars *
身处这里是你的权利
* you have a right to be here *
你是
* you are a child *
宇宙的孩子
* of the universe
身份不次于树木和星星
* no less than the trees and the stars *
身处这里是你的权利
* you have a right to be here *
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另招募长期居住海外的CC字幕录制童鞋（有酬劳）
联系QQ：864413459 注明：CC录制
你是
* you are a child *
宇宙的孩子
* of the universe *
身份不次于树木和星星
* no less than the trees and the stars *
身处这里是你的权利
* you have a right to be here *
你是
* you are a child *
宇宙的孩子
* of the universe *
身份不次于树木和星星
* no less than the trees and the stars *
身处这里是你的权利
* you have a right to be here *
你是
* you are a child *
宇宙的孩子
* of the universe *
身份不次于树木
* no less than the trees... *